<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<android.support.constraint.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".RulesAndRegulations">

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView123"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="Rules And Regulations"
        android:textAlignment="center"
        android:textColor="@android:color/black"
        android:textSize="20sp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/textView123"
        tools:layout_editor_absoluteX="0dp">

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/textView122"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginEnd="8dp"
            android:layout_marginStart="8dp"
            android:padding="3sp"
            android:text='1. The inmates bear full responsibility for the security of lightings, furniture,etc. Proper inventory is to be maintained at the time of allotment of room. At the time of leaving the room, all items should be in working condition. Damage caused would be dealt by the resident of room.\n2. Hostel Inmates are not allowed to permit any outsider in their rooms in hostel, without prior permission of Hostel waden.\n3. The inmate shall be responsible for all his belongings. Hostel authorities shall not be accountable for any loss/damage.\n4. Ragging is a cognizable offence and hence any student found indulged in it shall be seriously dealt with. \n5. Smoking, Consumption of liquor,drugs,etc is strictly prohibited.\n6. The Students are advised not to misuse electricity/water and observe cleanliness.\n7. There is a dispensary, with services of two doctors. In case of medical problem, if the student needs to go out of campus for checkup, all expenses will be borne by student/parents.\n8. Every student has to mark his digital attendance as per instructions.\n9. In any conflict, the decision of the Chief Warden shall be final.\n10. It is important for the student to report ragging done to him or if he finds someone being ragged.\n11. It is the duty of student to notify of change of his Permanent Address/Telephone No. as it might be needed in case of Emergency.\n         "We Wish You A Happy Stay."'
            android:textAlignment="textStart"
            android:textColor="@android:color/background_dark"
            app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
            app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.0"
            app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
            tools:layout_editor_absoluteY="0dp" />
    </ScrollView>

</android.support.constraint.ConstraintLayout>